{
  "prompt": "Use the distributive principle to solve the problem. Click the tile with the answer. ",
  "congratulations": "Congratulations! You have solved all the problems!",
  "font_size": "24px",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "3(x + 2)",
      "answer": "3x + 6"
    },
    {
      "question": "2(3 - x)",
      "answer": "6 - 2x"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3(x + 1)",
      "answer": "-3x - 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "4(2x - 3)",
      "answer": "8x - 12"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2(4x + 3)",
      "answer": "-8x - 6"
    },
    {
      "question": "2(3 - 4x)",
      "answer": "6 - 8x"
    },
    {
      "question": "2(3 + 4x)",
      "answer": "6 + 8x"
    },
    {
      "question": "6(3 - x)",
      "answer": "18 - 6x"
    },
    {
      "question": "4(3x - 1)",
      "answer": "12x - 4"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4(1 + 3x)",
      "answer": "-4 - 12x"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3(3x + 2)",
      "answer": "-9x - 6"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3(3x - 2)",
      "answer": "-9x + 6"
    },
    {
      "question": "2(2x + 5)",
      "answer": "4x + 10"
    },
    {
      "question": "6(x - 2)",
      "answer": "6x - 12"
    },
    {
      "question": "5(2x - 1)",
      "answer": "10x - 5"
    },
    {
      "question": "4(2 - 2x)",
      "answer": "8 - 8x"
    }
  ]
}
